Privacy Policy

Effective Date: 07/02/2024

Angeion Group, LLC (“Angeion Group,” “we,” “us” or “our”) respects your privacy online.

When you visit one of our websites (collectively, the “Site”) we adhere to the practices

described in this online privacy policy (this “Policy”). Please read the following Policy to

understand how information collected during your interaction with the Site will be treated.

If you do not agree with this Policy, then you are not authorized to use the Site. By

accessing or using the Site, you agree to this Policy.

This Policy applies only to the information collected about you through the Site or

provided to us by a third party and/or affiliate under your direction and/or control. It does

not apply to information collected via other channels or other websites that are owned or

operated by affiliate organizations on which this Policy is not posted.

We review our privacy practices from time to time, which are subject to change without

notice. Your continued use of the Site after we make any change is deemed to be your

acceptance of these changes and it is your obligation to check this Policy periodically to

ensure familiarity with the most current version of our privacy statement. The most

current version of our Policy will be posted on the Site. If you have any questions about

our privacy practices, you may contact us at support@angeiongroup.com.

Information We Collect

Automatic Information We Collect. When you visit the Site, we automatically collect

information about the IP address from which you access the site, the pages you visit, the

date and time you access our site, and the type of browser and operating system that you

are using. The information we compile is used to enhance the visitor’s experience when

using the website to display personalized content.

Information You Provide to Us. We may collect certain information you provide to us

directly and/or indirectly through a third party as per your authorization and/or control

when using the Site, such as, but not limited to, your name, address, telephone numbers,

mailing address, banking information for use in electronic payments, e-mail address and

interests.

Information from Third-Party Clients. We receive personal information about you from our

third-party clients, including law firms for which we provide, inter alia, settlement

administration and related services. Information we receive from third-party clients is not

governed by this Policy.

How We Collect Information

Automatic Information Collection

Information Collected by Cookies and Other Technologies. A “cookie” is a small file placed on

your device when you visit a site that can be understood by the site that issued the cookie.

We use cookies and other technologies, including device identifiers, to collect information

and support certain features of the Site. For example, we may use these technologies to:

• Collect information about the ways visitors use the Site—for example, which pages

they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page;

• Support the features and functionality of the Site—for example, to save you the

trouble of reentering information already in our database or to prompt the settings

you established on previous visits;

• Personalize your experience when you use the Site; and

• Improve our marketing efforts, including using targeted advertising.

The information we collect using cookies and similar technologies may or may not be

directly personally identifiable, but we may link it to personal information that you provide

or is otherwise collected during your use of the site. If you do not wish to receive cookies,

you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your

computer. Although you are not required to accept cookies when you visit the Site, you

may be unable to use all functionality of the Site if your browser rejects our cookies,

including the ability to submit a claim if all cookies are rejected.

Information Provided by You

E-Mail Content and Newsletters. You may choose to provide us with personal information

in an e-mail message to one of the addresses listed throughout the Site or by submitting

your information in the “Contact” section of the Site. We use this information to respond

to your message or to register you for the services you have requested. We may also use

this information to market or promote relevant services to you. If you sign up for an e-mail

newsletter, you have the option to unsubscribe at any time. Any information you choose

to provide regarding special interests may be used for marketing and promotional

purposes. By providing this information, you may receive occasional e-mail messages from

us.

Job Applications. We may collect certain personal information you provide to us when

applying for a job on the Site, including, but not limited to your name, address, telephone

numbers, mailing address, and e-mail address. Information collected in the application

process is excluded from the personal information described throughout this Policy.

Additional Sources of Information. You may provide additional information to us when you

request information or an estimate for our services. We may receive this information from

you through email, the website, or by phone.

How We Use Information

We use your personal information to provide you services, enhance your experience on

the Site, improve our services, and market and provide promotional activities. For more

details about how we use information, please see below.

Use of Information You Provide to Us. Generally, we may use information you provide to us

through the Site:

• To provide the information, products and services you request;

• To initiate electronic payments;

• For security or fraud prevention purposes;

• To provide you customer service;

• To provide you with a personalized experience when you use the Site;

• To contact you with information and notices related to your use of the Site;

• To better understand your needs and interests;

• To improve the content, functionality and usability of the Site;

• To improve our products and services;

• To improve our marketing and promotional activities; and

• For any other purpose identified in an applicable privacy notice, click-through

agreement, or other agreement between you and us.

Please see below for information about the choices you have about the ways we use your

personal information.

Use of Aggregated Information. We may use information gathered through the Site to create

a compiled, aggregate view of the Site’s audiences and its visitors’ usage patterns. We use

aggregated information to operate our services and to better understand our audience as

we develop new products and services. We may also share aggregated information with

our third-party service providers as well as with potential investors, advertisers, vendors,

and subscribers so they can better understand and/or market to our audience.

Third-Party Cookies and Interest-Based Advertising

In addition to the cookies we deliver to your computer or mobile or tablet device through

the Site, certain third parties may deliver cookies to you for a variety of reasons. For

example, we currently use Google Analytics, a web analytics tool that helps us understand

how visitors engage with the Site. To learn more about Google Analytics, click here. To

learn more about how Google uses data collected through partner sites or applications,

click here.

Other third parties may deliver cookies to your computer or mobile or tablet device for

the purpose of tracking your online behaviors across nonaffiliated websites and delivering

targeted advertisements either on the Site or on other websites.

For detailed information about the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use

them, please review our Cookie Policy.

Third-Party Data Sharing and Disclosure

Compliance with Law or Protection of Rights. We may disclose your personal information

when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law, a court

order, or a subpoena. We may also disclose your personal information to prevent or

investigate a possible crime such as fraud or identity theft; to protect the security of the

Site; to enforce or apply any applicable terms of use or other agreements; or to protect

our own rights or property or the rights, property, or safety of our users or others.

Business Negotiations. We may contemplate, for strategic or other reasons, selling, buying,

merging, or otherwise reorganizing one or more of our businesses. In negotiating with a

third party about entering into such an arrangement, we may need to disclose your

personal information. In such cases, we will take reasonable measures to protect the

personal information we disclose. For example, we may do so by requiring a prospective

purchaser to sign a non-disclosure agreement limiting the use and protecting the

confidentiality of the personal information.

Business Transfers. We may transfer the personal information you submit on or through

the Site to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, transfer of

control, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all

of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar

proceeding. In this case, personal information held by us about the Site’s users could be

transferred with other assets.

Vendors. Angeion Group may from time to time retain third-party vendors in order to help

us manage the Site and allow us to better serve our visitors and customers. These may

include third-party vendors we engage to analyze the information we collect for marketing

or similar purposes. We may contract with third parties who use cookies to collect

information on our behalf. These parties maintain their own confidentiality and security

standards. If you would like to opt out of this use of your information, you can change the

preferences of your browser so that it does not accept cookies. We may contract with

companies or others to provide certain services, including payment services, data

management, promotional services, etc. We provide these service providers with the

information they need to perform these services.

We may also share personal information to third-party vendors to help us provide you

services. For example, we use Amazon Web Services as a hosting provider. Such vendors

have access to personal information for a limited purpose and for a limited period, and we

implement contractual protections limiting the use of that personal information to the

provision of services to us.

Your Choices

In General. We respect your right to make choices about the ways your personal

information is collected and used. For example, we will include instructions to unsubscribe

from communications in each electronic newsletter or promotional e-mail we send you.

Unsubscribe from Newsletters or Promotional Communications. We want to provide you

information that is valuable to you. If at any time you wish to be taken off our mailing lists,

please follow the unsubscribe instructions included in our communications to you, contact

us by e-mail at support@angeiongroup.com, or send us written notice via mail at the

address listed below. Please provide your full name, postal address, and e-mail address so

that we can find you on our mailing lists. Once we have the information we need, we will

remove you from our mailing lists as you have requested. Please give us a reasonable

amount of time to honor your request.

Opt-Out Links. We do not control how third parties use your information. You can opt-out

of certain third-party activities at the links below. To opt-out of Google Analytics, please

visit: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. To opt-out of certain ad functions,

please visit: https://youradchoices.com/control.

Do Not Track Mechanisms. Because of the changing state of technology and indecision

within the industry regarding the meaning of Do Not Track signals, we currently do not

make any guarantee that we will honor Do Not Track signals.

Third-Party Links

The Site contains links to other websites. We encourage all our partners, contributors, and

third parties to implement policies and practices that respect the privacy of our users;

however, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites or

activities of our partners, contributors, and third parties in how they handle your data.

Social Media. We provide links on the Site to our third-party social media pages to provide

you additional information and additional methods for communicating with us. We are not

responsible for the privacy practices and/or content of such websites.

California Consumer Privacy Act and California Shine the Light Law

If you are a California resident, the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) California

Civil Code 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your

personal information by certain of our members to third parties for the third parties’ direct

marketing purposes.

The CCPA gives you certain rights with respect to the processing of your personal data.

Under the CCPA, you may request information about our collection, use, and disclosure

of your personal information over the prior 12 months, and ask that we provide you with

the following information:

• Categories of and specific pieces of personal information we have collected about

you.

• Categories of sources from which we collect personal information.

• Purposes for collecting, using, or selling personal information.

• Categories of third parties with which we share personal information.

• Categories of personal information disclosed about you for a business purpose.

The CCPA also allows you to request that we delete your personal information, subject to

certain exceptions. Under the CCPA, a “sale” means providing to a third-party personal

information for valuable consideration. We have taken substantial steps to identify

whether any of our data sharing arrangements would constitute a “sale” under the CCPA,

and have maintained that we do not sell or rent personal information to unaffiliated third

parties for their advertising or marketing lists.

To make a request regarding your personal data or other rights under this section, please

send an email to support@angeiongroup.com.

Children Under the Age Of Eighteen

The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18 and/or the age of majority in

your state (“minor”), whichever is greater. Minors may not use the Site without the

permission of a parent or guardian. If you believe that a minor has submitted personal

information on or through the Site without the consent and supervision of a parent or

guardian, please contact us using the information provided below so that we can take

appropriate action.

This Policy May Change

This Policy describes Angeion Group’s current policies and practices with regard to the

personal information we collect through the Site. This Policy may change and we reserve

the right to update or modify this Policy at any time, without prior notice. When this Policy

changes, we will update the “effective date” at the top of this page. Be sure to check the

date at the top of the page to see if this Policy has been revised since your last visit.

Contact Us

For more information or questions, please contact us at:

Angeion Group

1650 Arch Street, Suite 2210

Philadelphia, PA 19103

United States

Email: support@angeiongroup.com
